Hello, my name is Ayaki Mita of Crown Pop. I am Ayaki Mita from Crown Pop.
Ibuki's room. I would like to welcome this person again.
Yes, I'm Ayaki Mita of Crown Pop. This is Momoaru Crown version and Kanako Momota.
Please give my regards to them.
So, today is July 12,
Kanako's birthday.
Yay!
Happy birthday!
29 years old
Lots of meat.
Yes, meat.
Yes, I would like to eat lots of meat
Meat is good.
I love meat.
You love meat?
What's your favorite food?
My favorite food is omu-rice.
Omelette rice? So cute!
Omu-rice.
What is it?
I like ice cream.
Oh, wait a minute. I also like French fries.
I like the thin ones.
I like the thin ones. I understand.
I'm good at making omu-rice, so maybe next time.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
What?
What's that?
Are you sure?
I'm good at it. I'm good at it.
Good at what? You're good at it?
Yeah, I'm good at it.
There's a little bit of a buzz,
You got a little chuckle in there, didn't you?
But I really love my mom's omu-rice,
I'll make it the same way.
Do you cook? You know, people ask me that, right?
Yes, I do.
I really don't cook much.
I don't do it everyday.
But I only have knowledge of my mother's cooking.
I've learned a lot from my mother's cooking.
I think I'm getting pretty close to her omelette rice.
Oh, I want to eat it!
I'd love to try it sometime.
Please do.
I'd love to.
Let's go to your place.
Nothing much, but this is what people look like when they're off.
Not much... well, not a lot of stuff, but...
I wanted to ask you something.
I wanted to ask you about something... something the staff was talking about today.
There really is a Jizo inside the house.There really is a Jizo inside the house!
What is it, Shizuoka Prefecture?
Shizuoka Prefecture has a lot of them.
Wow!
I wonder...
Tea, of course.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
All kinds of Shizuoka
Within Shizuoka Prefecture.
There are many cities in Shizuoka Prefecture.
There's all kinds of tea.
Furniture.
Furniture and other personal effects
There are so many things.
I buy things.
As you wish.
When we decided to buy Shizuoka, we decided to go with it.
It seems like you're buying more and more.
Wow!
I bought some Shizuoka tea.
I got it as a gift at the StuffRaFest.
When I was in a musical in Osaka.
I was in Osaka for a week.
I took it with me and drank one every day.
I drank one every day and said, "I'll do my best today.
Really? I'm glad I did. Tea is really a comforting drink, isn't it?
I drink tea whenever I feel like taking a break, even when I'm on site.
I was happy.
I'm glad. I'm glad I could be of help.
So, I look forward to working with you again this time.
Mr. Momoguro, is your 15th anniversary tour starting soon?
Yes, it is.
In four days? It starts in four days.
Kobe, starting in 4 days? This is the start? This is the start? Yes, we will start in Kobe, then move on to Aichi, Tokyo, Fukuoka, Hiroshima, Osaka, Miyagi, Niigata, and many other places in Japan.
We will be touring all over the country, and in Tokyo, we will be performing at Musashino Mori, Sports Plaza, and Miyarinna in October.
I will be touring in October at Musashino Mori, Sogo Sports Plaza, and Miyarinna in Tokyo.
It's a great tour!
We haven't had many tours in the past,
When we release an album or something, we usually go around the concept of the album,
This time is the 15th anniversary,
This time is the 15th anniversary, so it's going to be a new tour.
Yes, this is a new tour, so please come and see it.
I want to go!
I don't know...15th anniversary...you know...YUYOGI?
I couldn't go when it was held at the Tank Kan,
I wanted to go on the tour.
I'd love to go.
Anywhere in Japan.
Are you sure?
Of course.
As a staff member.
You'll join us?
This is The High River Lance again.
I can't let you do that kind of work.
We're too busy every day.
In Yucie or anytime.Yucie or anytime.
I want to go.
You did an amazing job. Thank you very much. I will do my best.
It's your 15th anniversary tour, what kind of live show is the tour going to be like?
The tour is really a series of meetings with everyone,
We had a lot of meetings and decided what kind of tour we wanted to do, and we were worried about the direction of the tour,
It's really new.
Wow.
I think people will be able to see a new side of us.
And since this is our 15th anniversary tour, we wanted to make the tour not only new,
We will also be performing songs that have been loved by many people,
I'm making this album with the hope that people will enjoy it while listening to the new version of the songs.
It's really fun. Monclo's live performance.
Really? Really?
I haven't been able to see it since they started to let us call out,
I couldn't go to the 15th anniversary,
But, when I was invited to back up Arline at Ayaka Nation, I was able to call out for him,
I was allowed to call,
That's right.
I played contra and contra diction at that time,
The call was great.
I was impressed by the call. Contra.
That's right. We just danced, so we didn't have ear monitors or anything.
So the cheering was so loud that I couldn't hear the music.
Hmmm...they were really enthusiastic.
I was really fired up to see the four of us performing on our 15th anniversary.
I always wanted to see the new exhibition.
You guys have started the show with a lot of calls, haven't you?
Yes.
Is it totally different?
Yes, it is. It's totally different.
I don't know, there were people who said they had forgotten about it, and there were others who said they remembered,
Some said they had forgotten about it, and others said they remembered.
But it's the calls that make it so much fun.
And I think it's also because of that. When you hear people's voices at a live concert, you start cheering again.
It's like I'm smiling naturally.
Even in a place that is definitely not a place to laugh.
When I see people who are working hard to reach the goal.
I look at them and smile.
What do you mean? I'm sure.
It makes me happy.
I get happy. Don't ever laugh.
You mean like a cool song?
I'm fine with that,
But when I'm waiting for them to pause like this,
When I'm waiting for them to pose, and I see them doing it like this,
I look at them. That makes you happy, doesn't it? And this kind of person, too.
Yes, that's right. At release events, we have recently started to allow people to take videos,
When I see people tagging and posting their videos afterwards, I'm kind of embarrassed,
I felt a little embarrassed because I was grinning a little.
I thought I was grinning more than I thought I was.
But everyone is giving me cute moments?
Yes, they do. They do.
Sometimes, they give me a half-lidded look, like, "You should pick this out now.
Yes, they do. Fans often choose the cutest ones.
It makes me happy. They are dedicated.I'm glad to hear that. You're dedicated.
Yes, that's right.
So, Kanako, do you always take something with you when you go on tour or on an expedition?
Basically, I bring everything with me, like pajamas and such.
Not the hotel ones? No, I just bring my pajamas.
I feel at home with my own woman.
I don't know.
So, pajamas, shampoo, my favorite things.
I try to bring as much as I can.
I'll bring it with me so that I can do it.
I understand.
What is Tamai's story?
The one where the cool guy wears an eye mask and sleeps,
Sleeping with an eye mask.
You know... Shocking.
He even brought his own eye mask,
For long distances,
I bring an eye mask when I have to travel a long distance.
I also bring an eye mask when I have to travel long distances.
What do you have?
A luxury item?
But I tend to swell easily,
I see.
I never forget to wear something like Meri-Kid.
On the road?
When I'm on the road, or in a hotel,
Do you wear them at home?
I wear them at home.
Wow, that's great!
I'm also the type of person who takes all my beauty products with me,
Like Piramus?
Yes, when I bring things like piramis. But every year it becomes a hassle to carry them in my carry-on, so I tend to put them in a big bag and take them with me,
Recently, I borrow them from my make-up artist.
Yes, that's right. It is necessary, but you get used to it, don't you? And the expeditions, too. It takes a lot of time, doesn't it? I mean, you don't have luggage.
Does it take time to pack up to the airport?
Does it? Really?
So soon?
I'm really fast.
I'm really...
Really.
It takes less than 10 minutes.
Wow.
So you can do it in the morning?
Yes. Like in the morning.
But I sometimes wake up just in time in the morning.
I usually try to make it through the whole day.
I'm not sure.
It's usually set in stone, so it's over in the blink of an eye.
Eh....
It's over.
It takes time.
I'm so worried that I have to take it out and check it several times.
Take it out? You let it out once after you put it in.
So polite. I'm sure this politeness comes out in many places, right?
Yes, it does. Probably.
How many times did you read today's flow?How many times did you read today's stream or something?
Hey. I'm sure you did.
I got it earlier.
I got it a while ago. You want to check it out as much as possible in advance,
That's right.
Like deciding what to wear tomorrow?
Yes, that's right. I'll put it on.
You've already put it on. At night.
Then, do you make plans to go somewhere with your friends, for example?
With friends.
You don't go out with friends very often.
I don't go out much, but if...
If you wanted to go out with me, then...
It would probably be very difficult.
Maybe the day before.
I'd probably start preparing a long time ago.
The day of?
That's when...
When things don't go as planned.
When it's...
Like rain?
Rain.
What about when you were going to go, but you couldn't make it this way because of the time?
That's totally fine.
I see.
Okay.
But you have a firm schedule, and you don't mind if it falls apart?
Yeah, I do. I do.
But I've never done it properly.
I've never made plans with friends to go on a trip,
My sister usually takes care of that,
But I've never made plans with my friends to go on a trip.
Even if she decides to go this way, I'm the type to go along with her.
She seems to be that type.
You don't have trouble adjusting to others at all?
Not at all.
I don't have an absolute preference,
Even if we go to Disney, I never say I want to ride this or do that.
That's your private life, right?
What about your work?
Do you have any particular thing you can't give up in your work?
Not really.
Like a routine?
I don't have a routine, and I don't notice if I don't do something,
Do you have a routine that you have to do at a certain time before you sing?
Do you have one?
I try not to make too much of it.
When I can't do it, I get impatient,
I get impatient.
I get anxious.
You get impatient, don't you?
I think it goes both ways. There are many patterns,
It's like an eye contact,
I eat this the night before.
It's like a calming influence on your hands,Like calming your hands,
Or members, or even Renni-chan,
When she leaves the house, she leaves with her left foot.
And so on,
I can't do it,
But I can't do it.
I can't do it that carefully, and when I can't do it, I feel like I have unfinished business,
I can't do it that carefully, and when I don't do it, I worry about feeling like I've left something undone,
So I try not to be too particular about it,
But when I get nervous, I do this or that.
Ah, you understand.
I know what you mean. When you leave the house.
Yes, that's right. I think it starts with my left foot.
There's something about it.
Also, it's something to drink before a concert,
Oh, really?
Is that so?
Maybe that's it.
Hey!
Lately, I've been worrying too much.
I tend to care too much,
I dare not care anymore,
I'm trying not to think about it too much.
I try not to think too much,
I think too much.
So, don't think too much,
So, even if I can't do something,
I try to think, "Oh well, I'll figure it out. I try to think like, "Oh well, I'll manage.
So I try to have a sense of responsibility,
I want to do everything perfectly,
or earnestness or gentleness,
I think there are many moments when such things constrict me.
It's amazing.
It's a kind of psychology.
So, by thinking in such a way, you may find it easier.
If you are thinking about it, it means that you want to succeed,
Because you have such a strong desire to succeed,
If I succeed,
It may be too strong at times.
That's right.
Yes.
It's about time, unfortunately.
Yes. Unfortunately,
Oh, I'm sorry.
We were just talking together.
Together.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hot.
I wish I could have gone in there without screwing up.
Now
If you wanted to go into clinical
Can I go out once?
I'll be fine.
I'm afraid not.
I'm afraid I don't have time for you.Time and
It will be time and
It's hot.
Huh?
Here we go.
Just a breath.
Just a breath, please.
Yes, so unfortunately it's time for you to go.
Yes.
So, I am sad to say, but I would like to end.
I'm sad to say that it's over, but we had a lot to talk about this time,
I was very happy.
Well, it was my pleasure too,
Thank you very much.
I am sure we will see each other again at various sites,
So, please talk to me a lot then.
Can I talk to you again?
May I?
I'll catch you.
I don't know if I should ask you to catch me, but...,
I'm sure you'll tell me all about what happened today.
And you, Renda,
You'll really do it.
Yes.
And I tell him not to notice,
But you're very aware of me, so I'm very busy,
I'm busy. I wonder if you'll do something for me.
No, no, no.
Very much.
I'd appreciate it.
I'm grateful for it. It hasn't happened yet, right?
Let's go out to eat somewhere.
That's right.
I thought it might not last.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
We'll do it this year at some point.
Is that OK with you?
We're both a little hesitant.
Yes, we are.
I'm sure we'll find the right time. It's delicious.
What's that? Meat. I like meat,
Omelet with rice.
Omelette rice.
Like omu-rice. Like omu-rice restaurants.
I'll check it out.
I'll look into it.
I'll have Kanako's.
I'll have the homemade omu-rice then.
Okay.
So, up to this point, I've been with Erena Mita of Crowdpop,
Kanako Momota.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!